[{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce51"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":17607,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce52"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":16269,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce53"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":17232,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce54"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":22597,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce55"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":10350,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce56"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":6458,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce57"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":27558,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":15799,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce59"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":13808,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":9391,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":7053,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":5403,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":14358,"answer":"LH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":30711,"answer":"PLH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce5f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"3QO3J","rt":11654,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce68"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":51599,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce69"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":22952,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":21956,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":8543,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":26388,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":52601,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":29837,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce6f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":18294,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce70"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":26714,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce71"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":6248,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":5086,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce73"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":5165,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce74"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":12224,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce75"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":5460,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce76"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"pinecone","subject":"O577M","rt":18265,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce7f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":68664,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce80"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":34347,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce81"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":17482,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce82"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":7988,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce83"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":25378,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce84"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":11647,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce85"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":24856,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce86"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":37259,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce87"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":43327,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce88"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":9838,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":26088,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":7447,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce8b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":16287,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce8c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":10766,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce8d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"AHBMC","rt":21250,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce96"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":25885,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":62392,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce98"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":32925,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce99"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":20972,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":15895,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":13199,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":45576,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":59171,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":16166,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfce9f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":21647,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcea0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":15520,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcea1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":24122,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcea2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":26296,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcea3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":10559,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcea4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"bravo","subject":"M675E","rt":11685,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":45861,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":33620,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":12177,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":25672,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":149152,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcec9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":27943,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfceca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":42723,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcecb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":150032,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcecc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":52445,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcecd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":12422,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcece"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":8455,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcecf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":7483,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfced0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":26209,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfced1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":11141,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfced2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"pinecone","subject":"HK4RU","rt":78685,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcedb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":74614,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcedc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":31014,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcedd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":44709,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcede"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":36196,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcedf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":39056,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":18832,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":69397,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":35679,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":13605,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":17372,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":22636,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":11709,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":25657,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":8478,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcee9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"SZH6M","rt":44348,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf20"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":63820,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf21"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":33742,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf22"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":29693,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf23"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":18389,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf24"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":38685,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf25"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":17274,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf26"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":26224,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf27"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":46537,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf28"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":40572,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf29"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":10360,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf2a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":10385,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf2b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":12019,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf2c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":17310,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf2d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":10954,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf2e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"18BB6","rt":33639,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf37"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":30533,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf38"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":11333,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf39"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":14635,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":9179,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":16435,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":11096,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":31708,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":34687,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf3f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":92784,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf40"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":11409,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf41"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":16009,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf42"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":16662,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf43"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":12960,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf44"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":7045,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf45"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"DXES9","rt":22576,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf4e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":33069,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf4f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":42275,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf50"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":10767,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf51"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":10594,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf52"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":61218,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf53"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":69872,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf54"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":115087,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf55"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":65878,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf56"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":40959,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf57"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":15845,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":16961,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf59"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":11404,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf5a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":15417,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf5b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":9739,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf5c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"bravo","subject":"137NC","rt":26303,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf65"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":17154,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf66"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":11655,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf67"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":17040,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf68"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":44879,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf69"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":78645,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":5894,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":23738,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":32199,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":28644,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":25671,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf6f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":8462,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf70"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":7112,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf71"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":19799,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf72"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":21753,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf73"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"charlie","subject":"R8PM2","rt":19633,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf7c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":59849,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf7d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":25720,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf7e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":20603,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf7f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":8095,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf80"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":23685,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf81"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":51415,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf82"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":34532,"answer":"IJBMXOND"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf83"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":34368,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf84"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":18288,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf85"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":10894,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf86"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":8767,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf87"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":8712,"answer":"GP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf88"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":39670,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":6803,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"J9XH8","rt":37725,"answer":"GC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf93"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":35954,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf94"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":24224,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf95"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":19227,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf96"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":8659,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":23537,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf98"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":15095,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf99"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":36558,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":80290,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":18655,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":8796,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":12592,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":7871,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcf9f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":11137,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfa0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":6357,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfa1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"6NY13","rt":13901,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfaa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":13167,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":27797,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":61005,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":99700,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":186786,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfaf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":13803,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":23171,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":42757,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":18984,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":55556,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":18255,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":11472,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":31878,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":51763,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfb8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"bravo","subject":"JFFAY","rt":110927,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":62325,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":57298,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":11115,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":7453,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":83663,"answer":"OX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":32058,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":23717,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":27505,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfc9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":21308,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":13947,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfcb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":11186,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfcc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":6738,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfcd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":14830,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfce"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":6254,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfcf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"A57EU","rt":41859,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfd8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":47152,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfd9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":33737,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfda"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":15731,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfdb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":7517,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfdc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":85715,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfdd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":22177,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfde"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":31614,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfdf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":48277,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":16464,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":12344,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":37690,"answer":"BML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":11548,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":13564,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":8374,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfe6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"charlie","subject":"YF1HS","rt":46271,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcfef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":56086,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":29754,"answer":"XE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":59590,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":39838,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":30787,"answer":"ZHKU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":8207,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":45399,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":21272,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":12615,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":24208,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcff9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":9298,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcffa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":7580,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcffb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":44559,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcffc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":39077,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfcffd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"charlie","subject":"HKSU4","rt":25917,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd006"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":14125,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd007"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":41487,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd008"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":18891,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd009"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":30681,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":18111,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":97083,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":14953,"answer":"IBO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":97043,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":22590,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd00f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":37018,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd010"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":8962,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd011"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":11268,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd012"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":31175,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd013"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":8706,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd014"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"HUGFJ","rt":17487,"answer":"CX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd01d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":58910,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd01e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":25166,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd01f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":12489,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd020"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":37904,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd021"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":80817,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd022"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":7400,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd023"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":22811,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd024"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":147125,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd025"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":36939,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd026"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":21015,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd027"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":11103,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd028"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":7228,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd029"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":16775,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd02a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":19803,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd02b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"F66QO","rt":13823,"answer":"FC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd034"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":66778,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd035"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":34736,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd036"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":31435,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd037"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":45802,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd038"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":51937,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd039"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":16760,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":44056,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":51737,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":36830,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":14782,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":27136,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd03f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":33904,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd040"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":22191,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd041"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":15185,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd042"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"charlie","subject":"RYVXA","rt":48932,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd04b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":13509,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd04c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":26276,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd04d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":31140,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd04e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":18112,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd04f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":75504,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd050"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":22540,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd051"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":20302,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd052"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":21501,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd053"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":30290,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd054"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":9059,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd055"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":18602,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd056"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":9682,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd057"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":13455,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd058"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":7429,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd059"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"SMXP5","rt":107897,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd062"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":20990,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd063"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":38535,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd064"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":74334,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd065"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":13903,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd066"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":69797,"answer":"AK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd067"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":17753,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd068"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":19887,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd069"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":77649,"answer":"GC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":49481,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":13158,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":19584,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":54652,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":14220,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd06f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":7381,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd070"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"charlie","subject":"4K1DG","rt":21173,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd079"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":90951,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":106705,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":46383,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":36197,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":33853,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":49393,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd07f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":44212,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd080"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":52493,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd081"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":56028,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd082"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":15729,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd083"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":16475,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd084"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":18549,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd085"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":21672,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd086"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":15388,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd087"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"charlie","subject":"5FETT","rt":23695,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd090"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":39754,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd091"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":65918,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd092"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":14768,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd093"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":9342,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd094"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":18697,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd095"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":23281,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd096"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":88032,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd097"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":21404,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd098"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":65725,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd099"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":9624,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd09a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":15040,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd09b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":12926,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd09c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":13100,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd09d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":9285,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd09e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"7EAJ1","rt":26129,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":67765,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0a8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":58757,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0a9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":75035,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0aa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":18480,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0ab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":29433,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":19086,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0ad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":37971,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0ae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":88236,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":45025,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":7275,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":21655,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":8954,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":19522,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":7048,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0b5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"delta","subject":"FUV6R","rt":15205,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":33555,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0bf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":18137,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":8879,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":7674,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":19223,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":37283,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":39127,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":57201,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":42528,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":14987,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":12478,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":5377,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":15694,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0cb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":5963,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd0cc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"delta","subject":"D2B1E","rt":11097,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd103"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":44595,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd104"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":19328,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd105"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":24742,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd106"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":18409,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd107"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":26721,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd108"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":14025,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd109"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":43244,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":63492,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":28775,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":8820,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":13742,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":12475,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd10f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":17208,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd110"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":12499,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd111"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"delta","subject":"987KZ","rt":11101,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":35883,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":13226,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":54657,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":52807,"answer":"FU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":118586,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd11f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":14747,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd120"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":19592,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd121"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":27119,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd122"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":14357,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd123"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":41033,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd124"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":27287,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd125"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":6992,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd126"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":19483,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd127"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":36788,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd128"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"delta","subject":"4GSTQ","rt":40501,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd148"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":15036,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd149"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":25549,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":28993,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":37540,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":33737,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":8818,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":26516,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd14f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":31471,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd150"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":46557,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd151"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":10442,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd152"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":10578,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd153"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":7018,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd154"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":32948,"answer":"LH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd155"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":26149,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd156"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"P1BZ9","rt":2517,"answer":"P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd15f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":19132,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd160"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":14759,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd161"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":12880,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd162"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":7200,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd163"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":161026,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd164"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":6555,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd165"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":16563,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd166"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":26562,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd167"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":27751,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd168"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":45148,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd169"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":8846,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd16a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":7471,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd16b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":20795,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd16c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":26339,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd16d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"echo","subject":"EN7PB","rt":34032,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd176"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":22059,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd177"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":36685,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd178"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":34637,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd179"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":14744,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":30392,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":29847,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":100318,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":71196,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":18003,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd17f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":10227,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd180"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":39475,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd181"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":24471,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd182"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":14215,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd183"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":6445,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd184"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"1EKS2","rt":23447,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":90702,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":13260,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":20881,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":10605,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":21458,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":18784,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1aa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":72799,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1ab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":69924,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":56929,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1ad"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":6167,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1ae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":9774,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1af"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":7027,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1b0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":24940,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1b1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":6821,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1b2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"KAK9U","rt":16210,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":81010,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":37665,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":16812,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":21760,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":44255,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":16040,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":48570,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1d9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":60473,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1da"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":31530,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":7603,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1dc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":17445,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1dd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":11128,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1de"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":11460,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1df"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":6618,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd1e0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"echo","subject":"QX48K","rt":23977,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd22e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":69879,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd22f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":26197,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd230"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":10714,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd231"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":21629,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd232"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":25188,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd233"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":39618,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd234"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":54871,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd235"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":71342,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd236"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":51120,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd237"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":12604,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd238"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":43328,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd239"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":17590,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd23a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":22475,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd23b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":19293,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd23c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"echo","subject":"SOGCE","rt":33610,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd245"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":94658,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd246"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":103354,"answer":"AXKD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd247"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":94074,"answer":"AZFKUDEGB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd248"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":39283,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd249"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":78750,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":24107,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":32846,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":68470,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":22429,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":8815,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd24f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":10552,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd250"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":9622,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd251"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":17436,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd252"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":10946,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd253"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"echo","subject":"W2WL2","rt":21444,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd25c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":36252,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd25d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":46093,"answer":"CAIOZFHJXKUD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd25e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":37174,"answer":"AIOZFHJXKUDEGB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd25f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":10288,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd260"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":70301,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd261"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":21663,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd262"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":48108,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd263"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":54930,"answer":"IJE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd264"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":32734,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd265"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":77848,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd266"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":22412,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd267"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":12379,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd268"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":74170,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd269"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":66170,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd26a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"echo","subject":"KBQPW","rt":62057,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd273"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":27870,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd274"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":79105,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd275"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":23962,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd276"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":114254,"answer":"KU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd277"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":40341,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd278"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":38225,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd279"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":74685,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":178977,"answer":"JO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":25178,"answer":"IF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":37312,"answer":"BZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":22952,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":14704,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd27f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":36336,"answer":"PLH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd280"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":17944,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd281"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"echo","subject":"W7WZ4","rt":24802,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":53653,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":30634,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":10723,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":6792,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":22120,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd28f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":43588,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd290"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":34490,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd291"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":25303,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd292"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":72528,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd293"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":7483,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd294"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":10620,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd295"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":14803,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd296"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":12251,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd297"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":10929,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd298"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"0W2TN","rt":17648,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2b8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":56492,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2b9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":90882,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":16284,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2bb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":16304,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2bc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":15666,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2bd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":7203,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":28309,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2bf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":45480,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":16210,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":19515,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":17913,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":6257,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":10986,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":12468,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"foxtrot","subject":"T4UDR","rt":12413,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2cf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":31428,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":28747,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":21915,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":16903,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":16672,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":97767,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":33758,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":80349,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":55224,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":16918,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2d9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":9503,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":7285,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":16843,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2dc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":7093,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2dd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"EW5F7","rt":10736,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2e6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":64774,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2e7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":61633,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2e8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":119867,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2e9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":19967,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ea"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":39941,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2eb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":27926,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":44021,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ed"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":36866,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":79202,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2ef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":12249,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2f0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":17961,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2f1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":15257,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2f2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":24389,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2f3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":9897,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd2f4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"foxtrot","subject":"9GVF0","rt":20346,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd314"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":49493,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd315"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":56841,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd316"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":14081,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd317"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":11980,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd318"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":49886,"answer":"JXD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd319"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":12111,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":37930,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":39565,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":45250,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":9254,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":6901,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd31f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":14334,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd320"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":39430,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd321"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":8780,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd322"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"foxtrot","subject":"GNFRF","rt":112358,"answer":"CO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd342"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":28312,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd343"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":42499,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd344"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":80442,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd345"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":91978,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd346"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":131081,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd347"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":13700,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd348"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":20984,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd349"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":55418,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":56103,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":38938,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":15409,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":7350,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":40081,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd34f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":19682,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd350"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"foxtrot","subject":"YGEAY","rt":30692,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd359"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":75749,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":27549,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":24404,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":201261,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":20532,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":16292,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd35f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":37563,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd360"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":47062,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd361"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":82614,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd362"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":14113,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd363"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":28257,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd364"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":11732,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd365"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":21818,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd366"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":11201,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd367"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"foxtrot","subject":"LJTDL","rt":15445,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd370"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":129127,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd371"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":54488,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd372"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":77495,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd373"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":55864,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd374"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":81901,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd375"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":20342,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd376"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":60835,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd377"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":55218,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd378"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":91241,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd379"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":20799,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd37a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":27039,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd37b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":15472,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd37c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":20497,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd37d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":16779,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd37e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"foxtrot","subject":"J39G9","rt":32053,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd387"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":51817,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd388"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":21148,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd389"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":13184,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":10036,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":17290,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":10479,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":34156,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":27040,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd38f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":43920,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd390"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":6998,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd391"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":10565,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd392"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":4281,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd393"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":15045,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd394"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":9107,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd395"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"LSRUK","rt":24043,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd39e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":39626,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd39f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":35101,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":74608,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":28067,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":97840,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":10966,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":49630,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":32743,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":15284,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":7799,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":10683,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3a9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":10169,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3aa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":22103,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":7345,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ac"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"golf","subject":"DON7Q","rt":15553,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3b5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":39298,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3b6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":58099,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3b7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":72749,"answer":"AIF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3b8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":138017,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3b9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":24498,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ba"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":8576,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3bb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":44186,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3bc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":39309,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3bd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":49150,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":19242,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3bf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":24431,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":17200,"answer":"GP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3c1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":22774,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3c2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":6205,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3c3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"OTVZR","rt":57643,"answer":"CX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3cc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":17663,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3cd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":38763,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ce"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":27627,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3cf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":16059,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":99256,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":17552,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":30149,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":38644,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":22525,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":40347,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":16027,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":9308,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":34538,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3d9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":36746,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"golf","subject":"3W8J9","rt":47088,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":79372,"answer":"AI"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":56677,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":32450,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":29972,"answer":"DB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":41243,"answer":"XE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":6265,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3e9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":44545,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ea"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":58794,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3eb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":21777,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":62168,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ed"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":8921,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":5018,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ef"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":37322,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3f0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":18633,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3f1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"golf","subject":"HP71D","rt":34372,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3fa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":36381,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3fb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":126235,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3fc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":63618,"answer":"OJD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3fd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":30959,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3fe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":22418,"answer":"HJDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd3ff"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":95535,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd400"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":43064,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd401"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":139831,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd402"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":15508,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd403"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":7002,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd404"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":12673,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd405"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":22275,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd406"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":49241,"answer":"BM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd407"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":35770,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd408"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"golf","subject":"KLYG7","rt":23126,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd411"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":127435,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd412"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":69384,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd413"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":38649,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd414"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":17873,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd415"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":30985,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd416"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":19041,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd417"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":46331,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd418"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":97141,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd419"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":99593,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":12182,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":16266,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":10193,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":23436,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":9463,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd41f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"golf","subject":"AJZV2","rt":38165,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd43f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":33765,"answer":"AI"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd440"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":9089,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd441"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":33861,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd442"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":9120,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd443"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":9477,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd444"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":20439,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd445"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":15618,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd446"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":27110,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd447"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":19132,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd448"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":8511,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd449"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":8903,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd44a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":5896,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd44b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":9029,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd44c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":6351,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd44d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VLTVY","rt":11475,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd456"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":38070,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd457"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":39353,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd458"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":14366,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd459"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":8465,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":8042,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":5875,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":15031,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":16368,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":18235,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd45f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":13758,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd460"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":10334,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd461"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":11826,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd462"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":19383,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd463"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":5359,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd464"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"WDOR4","rt":8472,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd46d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":55105,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd46e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":48791,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd46f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":15365,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd470"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":18634,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd471"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":15545,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd472"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":13195,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd473"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":50384,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd474"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":16291,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd475"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":19745,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd476"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":8711,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd477"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":21128,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd478"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":7754,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd479"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":14265,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd47a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":7659,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd47b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"AZ6AR","rt":13356,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd484"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":31578,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd485"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":33458,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd486"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":24747,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd487"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":14274,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd488"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":51368,"answer":"AX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd489"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":26310,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":19690,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":30408,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":30217,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":17277,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":20092,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd48f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":11302,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd490"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":35997,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd491"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":7544,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd492"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"G7CFM","rt":22855,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd49b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":18816,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd49c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":21971,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd49d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":16687,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd49e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":45428,"answer":"FU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd49f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":95545,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":7551,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":11893,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":24505,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":15668,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":23695,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":17398,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":10138,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":17881,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":22865,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"LST9D","rt":38260,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":41486,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":26880,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":10288,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":7864,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":12543,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":14825,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":26216,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4b9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":46961,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":101931,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4bb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":9101,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4bc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":7884,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4bd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":7949,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":10826,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4bf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":5624,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"XY7JT","rt":21366,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":22137,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":34493,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4cb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":11440,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4cc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":10196,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4cd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":19430,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ce"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":20585,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4cf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":28159,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":42608,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":36121,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":11208,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":14977,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":9726,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":21398,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":11783,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4d7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"ZSBDA","rt":17812,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":24737,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":40532,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":28507,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":14136,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":70592,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":9186,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":70219,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":31829,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":50519,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4e9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":10320,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ea"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":9672,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4eb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":7912,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":8649,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ed"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":4371,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ee"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"3OTEP","rt":18961,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4f7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":60482,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4f8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":57811,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4f9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":20716,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4fa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":6419,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4fb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":59016,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4fc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":53686,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4fd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":35455,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4fe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":18987,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd4ff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":9607,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd500"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":9156,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd501"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":10661,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd502"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":6081,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd503"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":12568,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd504"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":7385,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd505"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"hotel","subject":"8DU2W","rt":14905,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd50e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":63923,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd50f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":13708,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd510"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":23465,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd511"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":14335,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd512"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":19461,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd513"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":13259,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd514"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":33229,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd515"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":62936,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd516"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":77186,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd517"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":16392,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd518"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":18272,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd519"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":25235,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd51a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":13770,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd51b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":10228,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd51c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"hotel","subject":"VARPG","rt":18145,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd525"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":39332,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd526"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":60112,"answer":"JK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd527"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":49764,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd528"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":11609,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd529"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":25384,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":6446,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":19918,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":29999,"answer":"HZND"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":18903,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":13850,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd52f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":15154,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd530"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":15512,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd531"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":52981,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd532"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":22328,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd533"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"QB8G8","rt":89436,"answer":"GC"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd53c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":26169,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd53d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":45701,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd53e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":33151,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd53f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":30138,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd540"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":23268,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd541"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":11769,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd542"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":58510,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd543"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":54046,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd544"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":28332,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd545"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":9033,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd546"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":12489,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd547"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":7406,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd548"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":18140,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd549"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":7920,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd54a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"DF15K","rt":19935,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd553"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":45700,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd554"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":48541,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd555"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":21779,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd556"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":14079,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd557"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":31012,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd558"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":16513,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd559"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":41872,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":62513,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":51112,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":5415,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":10847,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":10409,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd55f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":22521,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd560"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":10436,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd561"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"DDGO8","rt":15982,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":11080,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":9763,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":44051,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":49074,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":125414,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd56f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":6913,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd570"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":24445,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd571"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":24490,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd572"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":23622,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd573"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":47687,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd574"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":9357,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd575"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":5317,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd576"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":35015,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd577"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":19104,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd578"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"HH4FP","rt":25604,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd581"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":89874,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd582"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":40504,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd583"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":16979,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd584"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":21224,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd585"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":48415,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd586"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":12460,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd587"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":37740,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd588"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":65049,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd589"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":73207,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":13241,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":16931,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":6388,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":14554,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":5169,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd58f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"hotel","subject":"H7T38","rt":9922,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd598"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":43481,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd599"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":21890,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":22080,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":50725,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":161121,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":9549,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":31043,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd59f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":58892,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":17545,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":23793,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":15924,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":11560,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":40456,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":9137,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5a6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"7L4J4","rt":82157,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":21692,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":19771,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":41538,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":30520,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":31297,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":49357,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":57412,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":66405,"answer":"IJEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":60544,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":7966,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5b9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":12464,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5ba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":11087,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5bb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":15451,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5bc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":7389,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5bd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"FTCQC","rt":15939,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":45842,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5c7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":47936,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5c8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":43079,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":24569,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":98643,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5cb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":6780,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5cc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":45686,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5cd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":63601,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5ce"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":59133,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5cf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":16055,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5d0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":14314,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5d1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":8792,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5d2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":13965,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5d3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":7525,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5d4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"hotel","subject":"68W24","rt":16561,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5dd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":25980,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5de"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":18318,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5df"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":25148,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":75325,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":111684,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":6740,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":21583,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":55819,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":102214,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":8881,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":11874,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":5908,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5e9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":40658,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5ea"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":6522,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5eb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"B3OKB","rt":34206,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":49628,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":18011,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":69713,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":76604,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":56271,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5f9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":9367,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5fa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":52738,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5fb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":46892,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5fc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":26217,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5fd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":54870,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5fe"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":9137,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd5ff"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":12454,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd600"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":20746,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd601"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":18386,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd602"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"hotel","subject":"ZZYXF","rt":83137,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd60b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":23958,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd60c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":36420,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd60d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":15497,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd60e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":58745,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd60f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":91909,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd610"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":10689,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd611"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":16185,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd612"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":39903,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd613"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":42002,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd614"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":21642,"answer":"IJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd615"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":12390,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd616"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":10142,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd617"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":46198,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd618"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":45047,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd619"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"hotel","subject":"8V51R","rt":53057,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd622"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":78634,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd623"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":16626,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd624"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":18095,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd625"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":4932,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd626"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":13663,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd627"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":4786,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd628"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":16000,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd629"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":38167,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":54338,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":5665,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":8081,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":8737,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":19358,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd62f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":8455,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd630"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SRVE3","rt":8018,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd639"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":25936,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":11444,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":12896,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":41055,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":57440,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":8614,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd63f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":33216,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd640"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":58174,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd641"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":16139,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd642"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":6612,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd643"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":12518,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd644"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":11820,"answer":"GP"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd645"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":12697,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd646"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":7128,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd647"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"E4JSN","rt":8758,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd650"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":14742,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd651"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":27637,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd652"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":20840,"answer":"FD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd653"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":8001,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd654"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":49942,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd655"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":7264,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd656"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":28705,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd657"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":22101,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd658"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":30577,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd659"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":6353,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd65a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":11466,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd65b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":6563,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd65c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":12602,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd65d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":6162,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd65e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"SH7C5","rt":31177,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd667"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":44697,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd668"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":25216,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd669"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":11250,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":9894,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":16210,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":16595,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":26495,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":44333,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd66f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":29021,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd670"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":6115,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd671"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":15156,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd672"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":9206,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd673"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":16615,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd674"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":9142,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd675"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"M6DP5","rt":15896,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd67e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":54011,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd67f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":48451,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd680"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":21066,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd681"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":12602,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd682"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":18056,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd683"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":11082,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd684"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":23410,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd685"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":30984,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd686"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":43169,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd687"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":7222,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd688"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":11785,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd689"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":6238,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd68a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":12167,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd68b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":10778,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd68c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"UKWDH","rt":12417,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd695"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":56289,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd696"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":21337,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd697"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":12187,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd698"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":7837,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd699"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":24206,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":25178,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":29199,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":59950,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":49582,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":10487,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd69f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":10822,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6a0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":6753,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6a1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":20724,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6a2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":7243,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6a3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"NSPM3","rt":16196,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ac"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":35104,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ad"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":23830,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":26851,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6af"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":14025,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":21237,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":9470,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":29050,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":31947,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":45534,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":8953,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":12646,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":8654,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":12940,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6b9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":9525,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"7Q7KP","rt":15744,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":20244,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":69739,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":12685,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":9503,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":87506,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":10092,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":48191,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":27659,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6cb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":17331,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6cc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":9749,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6cd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":12349,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ce"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":8547,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6cf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":12796,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6d0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":22103,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6d1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"R0GKA","rt":13559,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":46119,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":70336,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6dc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":19317,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6dd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":55361,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6de"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":72965,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6df"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":19466,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":23913,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":33712,"answer":"IJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":13047,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":10806,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":7804,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":23353,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":17918,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":8846,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6e8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"1FO1D","rt":24291,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":59708,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":28846,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":14602,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":13199,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":47765,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":35763,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":24587,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":30365,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6f9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":51793,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6fa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":10288,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6fb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":10771,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6fc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":7471,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6fd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":28036,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6fe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":7076,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd6ff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"DOS1L","rt":16033,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd708"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":56939,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd709"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":15016,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":16618,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":34073,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":41252,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":11691,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":21022,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd70f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":67176,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd710"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":94253,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd711"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":9427,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd712"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":13292,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd713"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":6216,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd714"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":12386,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd715"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":14757,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd716"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"NL1H0","rt":19505,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd71f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":50332,"answer":"AI"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd720"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":27073,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd721"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":10404,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd722"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":8165,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd723"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":12448,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd724"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":43194,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd725"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":27957,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd726"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":21403,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd727"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":31999,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd728"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":10538,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd729"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":16418,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd72a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":6764,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd72b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":29873,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd72c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":8116,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd72d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"DUV1M","rt":42773,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd74d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":59954,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd74e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":37134,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd74f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":22966,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd750"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":16240,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd751"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":19932,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd752"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":14291,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd753"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":40671,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd754"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":41661,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd755"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":56840,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd756"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":15232,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd757"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":17960,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd758"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":8495,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd759"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":16674,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd75a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":7900,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd75b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"BCFGX","rt":13872,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd764"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":70968,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd765"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":57598,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd766"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":37780,"answer":"JK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd767"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":22735,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd768"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":18233,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd769"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":16961,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":26898,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":62525,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":21470,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":16946,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":16252,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd76f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":20360,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd770"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":46871,"answer":"EH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd771"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":27411,"answer":"P"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd772"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"2O3GE","rt":15356,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd77b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":35685,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd77c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":88024,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd77d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":14814,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd77e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":9733,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd77f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":49821,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd780"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":13777,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd781"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":36790,"answer":"XOH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd782"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":30599,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd783"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":29748,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd784"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":9044,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd785"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":13818,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd786"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":11248,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd787"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":13827,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd788"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":5088,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd789"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"2VK07","rt":16149,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd792"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":24813,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd793"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":34591,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd794"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":7747,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd795"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":45534,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd796"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":90478,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd797"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":5272,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd798"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":21688,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd799"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":18909,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":14134,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":51491,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":8492,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":6825,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":20790,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd79f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":62758,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7a0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"india","subject":"GF1FQ","rt":23948,"answer":"EB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":16928,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7aa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":15828,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ab"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":17449,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":55245,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ad"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":143273,"answer":"HU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":14450,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":28393,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":76616,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":49428,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":44757,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":7596,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":7287,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":31701,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":20629,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7b7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"N53LC","rt":49322,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":39035,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":20632,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":33368,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":12011,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":99583,"answer":"HE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":43082,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":47460,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":78998,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":27348,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":8224,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":9916,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7cb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":9746,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7cc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":15432,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7cd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":8600,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ce"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"india","subject":"R2JGD","rt":36225,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7d7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":62552,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7d8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":29472,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7d9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":13340,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":10519,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":84047,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7dc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":8611,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7dd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":29851,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7de"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":102479,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7df"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":54285,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":21525,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":16066,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":12184,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":19347,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":7482,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7e5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"india","subject":"74C5E","rt":15462,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":19547,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7ef"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":16941,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":16722,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":29764,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":31988,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":6973,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":21009,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":44650,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":15839,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":30099,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":9310,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7f9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":7895,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7fa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":31513,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7fb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":36539,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd7fc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"QSGCP","rt":32148,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd805"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":26552,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd806"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":27636,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd807"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":43636,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd808"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":64451,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd809"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":90949,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":7391,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":18647,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":48723,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":15037,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":20599,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd80f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":10782,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd810"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":7468,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd811"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":15957,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd812"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":19283,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd813"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"TX10R","rt":94110,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd81c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":23208,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd81d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":26070,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd81e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":44980,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd81f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":106018,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd820"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":156974,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd821"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":7161,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd822"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":20594,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd823"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":38467,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd824"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":20855,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd825"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":28502,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd826"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":18107,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd827"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":12437,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd828"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":25511,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd829"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":44535,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd82a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"india","subject":"2BBZ9","rt":26737,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":21755,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":54805,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":22290,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":61155,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":17731,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd84f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":107385,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd850"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":37355,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd851"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":44875,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd852"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":23336,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd853"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":18010,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd854"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":13507,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd855"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":11691,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd856"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":15420,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd857"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":6943,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd858"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"india","subject":"JFJSX","rt":110276,"answer":"CO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd861"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":56137,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd862"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":67084,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd863"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":24498,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd864"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":17491,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd865"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":99195,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd866"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":15662,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd867"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":41391,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd868"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":76980,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd869"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":99776,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":13999,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":15810,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":9197,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":17436,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":8453,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd86f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"india","subject":"KPQ3L","rt":13656,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd878"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":30768,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd879"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":59330,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":15396,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":15499,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":21634,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":23494,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":42476,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd87f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":23860,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd880"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":46150,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd881"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":9786,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd882"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":13705,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd883"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":15220,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd884"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":12415,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd885"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":5230,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd886"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"WDUSF","rt":12259,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd88f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":52247,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd890"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":19988,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd891"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":27184,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd892"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":55796,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd893"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":117300,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd894"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":6499,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd895"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":24905,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd896"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":38789,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd897"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":21451,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd898"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":24314,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd899"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":10825,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd89a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":6366,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd89b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":42690,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd89c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":33688,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd89d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"N2UK6","rt":80040,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":39749,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":31255,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8a8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":42137,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8a9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":88991,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8aa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":35060,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ab"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":11838,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":16883,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":27199,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":25723,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":35583,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8b0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":16240,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8b1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":6521,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8b2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":54829,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8b3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":16970,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8b4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"juliet","subject":"C68PP","rt":14586,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8bd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":46040,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8be"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":22305,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8bf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":15722,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":74084,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":83132,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":11019,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":16986,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":38839,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":21192,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":26924,"answer":"XZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":11860,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":8877,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8c9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":26993,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ca"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":41849,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8cb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"111","subject":"EFTYS","rt":43055,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":40873,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":12541,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":12785,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":14975,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":13549,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8d9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":10208,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":27980,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":29975,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8dc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":35728,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8dd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":13694,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8de"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":13407,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8df"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":10519,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8e0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":14821,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8e1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":10145,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8e2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"kilo","subject":"OQB9V","rt":10339,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8eb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":31595,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":57322,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ed"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":13371,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ee"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":13418,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8ef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":30142,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":17513,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":38223,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":48964,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":45233,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":14698,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":9904,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":12775,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":18293,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":8538,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd8f9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"juliet","subject":"LV9FA","rt":21989,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd902"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":71453,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd903"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":32850,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd904"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":26191,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd905"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":22585,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd906"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":44820,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd907"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":17262,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd908"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":59710,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd909"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":126993,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":69326,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":22982,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":31448,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":11139,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":24432,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd90f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":11016,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd910"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"juliet","subject":"M1REU","rt":40241,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd947"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":27885,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd948"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":67401,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd949"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":71930,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":123396,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":33799,"answer":"AF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":11635,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":39946,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":62816,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd94f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":18643,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd950"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":11926,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd951"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":12658,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd952"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":13258,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd953"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":41251,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd954"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":29334,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd955"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"FGMSN","rt":18451,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd95e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":35891,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd95f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":40820,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd960"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":18134,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd961"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":7816,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd962"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":63845,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd963"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":32905,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd964"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":37666,"answer":"XD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd965"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":32010,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd966"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":25241,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd967"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":6292,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd968"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":15517,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd969"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":14854,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd96a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":12055,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd96b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":10453,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd96c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"LY74F","rt":22378,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd98c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":45919,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd98d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":16753,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd98e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":11361,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd98f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":10623,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd990"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":22468,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd991"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":8883,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd992"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":47269,"answer":"XOH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd993"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":33911,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd994"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":13632,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd995"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":12892,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd996"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":12511,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd997"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":6792,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd998"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":18879,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd999"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":6630,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd99a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"BPUXY","rt":13675,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":41653,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":40793,"answer":"GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":38884,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":10283,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":23845,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":9132,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":15338,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9aa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":34008,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ab"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":15509,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":32262,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":9713,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":6130,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":27615,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9b0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":17661,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9b1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"L0M3H","rt":46926,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ba"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":16670,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9bb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":14351,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9bc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":25442,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9bd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":34228,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":31136,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9bf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":11903,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":19059,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":23518,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":29348,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":31687,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":14980,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":12332,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":22957,"answer":"BX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":20733,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9c8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"F58KT","rt":69245,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":49973,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":45671,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":39640,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":31330,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":32149,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":54693,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":41931,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":40486,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9d9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":11956,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9da"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":10368,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9db"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":20166,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9dc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":6745,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9dd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":14981,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9de"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":5989,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9df"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"DF3OH","rt":17844,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9e8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":96302,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9e9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":83282,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ea"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":17350,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9eb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":10838,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":43322,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ed"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":28884,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":48608,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9ef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":48095,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":53050,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":43774,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":29237,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":10072,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":25875,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":7977,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfd9f6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"juliet","subject":"RVFBM","rt":13809,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda16"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":67709,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda17"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":35471,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda18"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":17566,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda19"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":11407,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":17828,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":52640,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":46072,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":58473,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":50871,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda1f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":10075,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda20"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":10760,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda21"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":7527,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda22"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":26720,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda23"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":6921,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda24"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"7TRHG","rt":13322,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda2d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":55659,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda2e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":14667,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda2f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":11623,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda30"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":12161,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda31"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":36165,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda32"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":11230,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda33"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":25757,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda34"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":61629,"answer":"IJEF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda35"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":52622,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda36"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":7254,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda37"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":12444,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda38"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":11938,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda39"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":23112,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda3a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":8035,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda3b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"ACPUO","rt":11983,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda44"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":12464,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda45"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":24498,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda46"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":12351,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda47"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":46281,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda48"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":41750,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda49"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":112690,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":41543,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":149045,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":42566,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":24614,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":10750,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda4f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":9103,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda50"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":17043,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda51"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":34992,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda52"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"juliet","subject":"TCJQ2","rt":19800,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda5b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":40456,"answer":"AI"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda5c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":23843,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda5d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":82876,"answer":"AI"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda5e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":68575,"answer":"OF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda5f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":69646,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda60"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":7900,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda61"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":17245,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda62"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":34710,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda63"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":23405,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda64"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":52168,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda65"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":7847,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda66"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":4928,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda67"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":16887,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda68"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":14460,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda69"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"ASEGP","rt":26363,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":44186,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda73"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":34631,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda74"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":47209,"answer":"ZFHJXKUDEGB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda75"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":59981,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda76"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":85862,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda77"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":8497,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda78"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":17099,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda79"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":26453,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":16499,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":17764,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":9248,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":7444,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":48928,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda7f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":11280,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda80"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"PO9J4","rt":37124,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":47214,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":38776,"answer":"KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":19690,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":99791,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":39020,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":6504,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda8f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":15341,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda90"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":45476,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda91"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":15363,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda92"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":14490,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda93"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":13930,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda94"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":19478,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda95"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":16214,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda96"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":9280,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfda97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"FD7Z1","rt":11949,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":51645,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":41565,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":30419,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":18317,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":64628,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":11218,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":53305,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":60829,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":33488,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaa9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":9298,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaaa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":16541,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":7173,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaac"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":15577,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaad"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":12522,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"KBCXA","rt":25934,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdab7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":27795,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdab8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":88824,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdab9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":94119,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":18358,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdabb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":30853,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdabc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":15294,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdabd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":51948,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdabe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":54721,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdabf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":88033,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":21866,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":16125,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":9783,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":26436,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":23658,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdac5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"OMHWY","rt":17746,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdace"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":15952,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdacf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":16576,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":27608,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":16238,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":46905,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":9512,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":48164,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":27625,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":22648,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":10256,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":12925,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdad9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":7521,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdada"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":30120,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdadb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":9566,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdadc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"G5XSH","rt":12481,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdae5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":67699,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdae6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":51600,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdae7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":36967,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdae8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":15652,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdae9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":16614,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaea"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":11327,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaeb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":21794,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":50623,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaed"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":23988,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaee"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":10794,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":16997,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaf0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":8426,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaf1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":15636,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaf2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":11783,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaf3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"TW03E","rt":14401,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdafc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":33241,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdafd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":31895,"answer":"KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdafe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":32511,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdaff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":16640,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb00"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":38651,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb01"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":9213,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb02"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":22816,"answer":"IJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb03"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":41058,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb04"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":122080,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb05"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":21617,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb06"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":8976,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb07"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":9881,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb08"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":14001,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb09"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":8622,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb0a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"kilo","subject":"MABX4","rt":12380,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb13"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":44719,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb14"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":39780,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb15"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":17896,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb16"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":19776,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb17"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":25525,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb18"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":33962,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb19"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":39815,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":40656,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":40953,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":9351,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":12311,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":6567,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb1f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":11304,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb20"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":8737,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb21"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"33WRC","rt":15811,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":56673,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":22137,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":52746,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":26106,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":80686,"answer":"AF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb2f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":31229,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb30"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":47240,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb31"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":74024,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb32"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":30253,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb33"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":11379,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb34"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":15562,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb35"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":10029,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb36"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":26464,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb37"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":7293,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb38"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"juliet","subject":"DC2Y0","rt":88787,"answer":"OH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb41"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":63980,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb42"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":10612,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb43"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":20287,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb44"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":9436,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb45"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":12747,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb46"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":10756,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb47"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":17513,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb48"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":23566,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb49"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":39421,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":18250,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":12090,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":15912,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":10644,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":6855,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb4f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"8970T","rt":10653,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":30727,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb59"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":19060,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":13954,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":13271,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":28802,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":52227,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":20580,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb5f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":25028,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb60"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":25751,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb61"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":14354,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb62"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":13114,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb63"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":8510,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb64"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":19266,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb65"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":8722,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb66"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"JO9RJ","rt":18107,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb6f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":44104,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb70"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":67090,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb71"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":22150,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":18871,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb73"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":31905,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb74"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":11761,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb75"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":62587,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb76"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":96657,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb77"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":29136,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb78"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":12209,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb79"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":14489,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb7a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":8222,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb7b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":22107,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb7c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":13776,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb7d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"7K5C9","rt":15811,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb86"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":24931,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb87"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":16626,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb88"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":38572,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":36018,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":32994,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":7666,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":28856,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":33575,"answer":"IJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":16044,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb8f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":60217,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb90"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":11950,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb91"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":8199,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb92"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":54275,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb93"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":49731,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb94"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"kilo","subject":"N8EYG","rt":21772,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":53721,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":24220,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdb9f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":20402,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":13893,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":51903,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":10069,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":24617,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":36604,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":30606,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":6156,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":9386,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":6748,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdba9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":12756,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbaa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":8218,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6CR5M","rt":13875,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":75013,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":31054,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":18923,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":24521,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":48569,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbb9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":13831,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":27303,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbbb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":76156,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbbc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":75939,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbbd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":9985,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbbe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":10697,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbbf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":8954,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbc0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":13357,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbc1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":5601,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbc2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"94FPA","rt":11793,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbcb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":30915,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbcc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":12185,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbcd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":30219,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbce"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":16205,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbcf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":39796,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":10937,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":26394,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":38447,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":21638,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":18913,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":10544,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":13923,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":24587,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":23401,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbd9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"6G1ZR","rt":38669,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":68086,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":13874,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":8945,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":12346,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":16165,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":6091,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":22671,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbe9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":24369,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbea"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":33690,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbeb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":13662,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbec"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":13740,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbed"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":6508,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbee"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":12183,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":7350,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbf0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VEVUZ","rt":24450,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbf9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":101863,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbfa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":66019,"answer":"KE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbfb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":43562,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbfc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":37990,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbfd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":18799,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbfe"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":25357,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdbff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":89331,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc00"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":59134,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc01"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":28580,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc02"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":14392,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc03"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":12969,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc04"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":13978,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc05"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":16922,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc06"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":15893,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc07"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"kilo","subject":"EPAUX","rt":17753,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc10"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":95660,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc11"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":51775,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc12"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":73707,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc13"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":41821,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc14"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":34624,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc15"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":53396,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc16"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":73645,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc17"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":33773,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc18"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":29703,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc19"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":7588,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc1a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":18388,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc1b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":7588,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc1c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":16922,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc1d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":13968,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc1e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"kilo","subject":"RM2SM","rt":14530,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc27"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":27101,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc28"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":16196,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc29"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":13655,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":8442,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":19956,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":32535,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":27777,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":35668,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc2f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":76511,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc30"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":8133,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc31"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":11187,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc32"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":13093,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc33"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":22314,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc34"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":7767,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc35"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"VUHEV","rt":13451,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc3e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":59810,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc3f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":17581,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc40"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":9956,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc41"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":6866,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc42"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":24996,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc43"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":6298,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc44"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":56980,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc45"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":39274,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc46"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":28186,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc47"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":9239,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc48"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":15774,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc49"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":8907,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc4a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":13959,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc4b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":7295,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc4c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"Q7P0Z","rt":12863,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc55"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":62685,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc56"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":38647,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc57"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":18452,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":28950,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc59"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":36285,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":54609,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":37715,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":49794,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":22490,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":19686,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc5f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":34533,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc60"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":10637,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc61"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":28703,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc62"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":8372,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc63"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"W857O","rt":18969,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc6c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":47088,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc6d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":41610,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc6e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":45962,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc6f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":11364,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc70"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":12886,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc71"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":11382,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":44270,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc73"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":35668,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc74"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":7053,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc75"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":24244,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc76"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":35569,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc77"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":14693,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc78"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":18328,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc79"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":6584,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc7a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"lima","subject":"LFDYR","rt":26921,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc83"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":45889,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc84"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":24928,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc85"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":17553,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc86"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":8338,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc87"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":30312,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc88"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":8419,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":30187,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":33620,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":31042,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":10132,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":10206,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":12751,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc8f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":10266,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc90"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":9839,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc91"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"VA4GG","rt":10628,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":36379,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":27840,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":22791,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":11277,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":40599,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdc9f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":11710,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":31425,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":69880,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":31837,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":6429,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":11949,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":12243,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":16974,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":9167,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdca8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"7RVE0","rt":18437,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":85775,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":42631,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":22238,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":34977,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":115844,"answer":"OHJKDE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":10803,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":59889,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":93044,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcb9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":42573,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":12633,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcbb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":16913,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcbc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":8951,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcbd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":17947,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcbe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":8961,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcbf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"kilo","subject":"UTZ96","rt":46412,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcc8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":41765,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcc9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":27093,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcca"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":28402,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdccb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":34338,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdccc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":39923,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdccd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":10409,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcce"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":17314,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdccf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":27759,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":26653,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":43304,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":8625,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":6073,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":47389,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":16449,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcd6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"G0CPA","rt":23049,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcdf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":14161,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":19458,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":24511,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":19805,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":115512,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":10985,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":19989,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":70884,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":29827,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":52046,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdce9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":7824,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcea"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":5542,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdceb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":42168,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcec"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":32713,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdced"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EENOM","rt":44915,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcf6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":29910,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcf7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":11859,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcf8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":31343,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcf9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":18939,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcfa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":24837,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcfb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":99533,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcfc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":39784,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcfd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":72746,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcfe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":52247,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdcff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":5528,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd00"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":11512,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd01"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":6349,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd02"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":15686,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd03"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":5784,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd04"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"lima","subject":"SAAFX","rt":12029,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd0d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":63610,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd0e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":34332,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd0f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":15611,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd10"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":20595,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd11"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":75091,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd12"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":15574,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd13"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":61197,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd14"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":84517,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd15"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":33718,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd16"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":7979,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd17"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":18407,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd18"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":5732,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd19"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":13314,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd1a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":14476,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd1b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"C1LJW","rt":16338,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd3b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":41473,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd3c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":22278,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd3d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":64255,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd3e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":100977,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd3f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":106492,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd40"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":10576,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd41"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":24959,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd42"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":75426,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd43"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":38714,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd44"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":28984,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd45"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":6688,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd46"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":20814,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd47"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":30797,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd48"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":15880,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd49"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"6VE21","rt":58403,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd52"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":16573,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd53"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":104949,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd54"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":25030,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd55"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":9848,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd56"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":120690,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd57"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":13669,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":66839,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd59"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":63830,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":41566,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":7036,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":10932,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":5571,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":16019,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd5f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":7118,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd60"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"lima","subject":"V8DLR","rt":55024,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd69"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":58152,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":36279,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":29966,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":28699,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":47976,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":34285,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd6f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":37632,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd70"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":27517,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd71"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":43266,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":8580,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd73"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":19536,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd74"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":18530,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd75"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":23080,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd76"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":8924,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd77"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"Y53PP","rt":13511,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd80"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":117343,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd81"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":37916,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd82"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":30942,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd83"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":46635,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd84"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":60467,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd85"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":12136,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd86"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":112156,"answer":"JB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd87"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":24450,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd88"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":16406,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":41322,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":24359,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd8b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":12602,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd8c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":37922,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd8d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":9307,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd8e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"lima","subject":"6S0HV","rt":18920,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":109183,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd98"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":32590,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd99"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":21738,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":15387,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":73388,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":19023,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":92488,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":44081,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdd9f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":29817,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":15173,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":16227,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":26668,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":26936,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":8557,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdda5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"lima","subject":"FXH2P","rt":20139,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddae"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":38747,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddaf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":26557,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":13667,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":47352,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":149386,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":14545,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":32229,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":31657,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":28436,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":67022,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":15957,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddb9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":8397,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddba"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":38033,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddbb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":34726,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddbc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"EC0K7","rt":32773,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddc5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":14316,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddc6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":42351,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddc7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":152741,"answer":"FKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddc8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":33866,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddc9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":100940,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddca"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":22181,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddcb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":31195,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddcc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":68332,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddcd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":30854,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddce"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":37516,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddcf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":30643,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddd0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":55409,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddd1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":11788,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddd2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":10068,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddd3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"lima","subject":"XQZYP","rt":27246,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdddc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":34899,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdddd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":11866,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddde"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":9443,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdddf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":7144,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":36406,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":20963,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":22497,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":30212,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":16116,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":10955,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":11097,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":8194,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":22963,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdde9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":8568,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddea"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"YA9CN","rt":71787,"answer":"AG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":12821,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":27604,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":46133,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":21252,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":16061,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":32170,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddf9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":26470,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddfa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":38766,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddfb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":10456,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddfc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":10887,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddfd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":13977,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddfe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":10132,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfddff"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":10538,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde00"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":7488,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde01"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"61C10","rt":10747,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":49174,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":33312,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":22070,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":31138,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":23805,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde0f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":6291,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde10"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":31210,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde11"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":57790,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde12"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":37651,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde13"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":8200,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde14"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":9175,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde15"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":6558,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde16"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":11362,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde17"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":6450,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde18"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"KUHF1","rt":11320,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde21"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":27155,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde22"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":32974,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde23"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":39846,"answer":"EB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde24"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":18376,"answer":"D"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde25"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":56959,"answer":"AO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde26"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":21567,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde27"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":19333,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde28"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":36093,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde29"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":19456,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":20652,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":8214,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":12253,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":27505,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":19519,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde2f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5EWM2","rt":35530,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde38"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":20684,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde39"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":11134,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":39739,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":11667,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":27231,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":9491,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":58538,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde3f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":55338,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde40"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":38588,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde41"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":7799,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde42"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":10968,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde43"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":8116,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde44"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":16671,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde45"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":7120,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde46"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"3ZLSF","rt":14321,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde4f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":138494,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde50"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":19382,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde51"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":22127,"answer":"AIF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde52"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":28108,"answer":"OF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde53"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":73627,"answer":"FU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde54"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":10127,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde55"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":13901,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde56"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":25957,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde57"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":22951,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde58"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":46518,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde59"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":8633,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde5a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":10819,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde5b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":18839,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde5c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":19830,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde5d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"1THJX","rt":21266,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde66"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":49388,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde67"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":28212,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde68"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":37501,"answer":"ZKUDEGB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde69"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":10046,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":21669,"answer":"OX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":22636,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":48557,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":22863,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":60578,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde6f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":34265,"answer":"M"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde70"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":13263,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde71"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":16212,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde72"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":16495,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde73"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":8822,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde74"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"H9B17","rt":51397,"answer":"HZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde7d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":55034,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde7e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":12183,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde7f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":14934,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde80"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":7433,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde81"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":17833,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde82"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":21469,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde83"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":43163,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde84"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":32895,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde85"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":85339,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde86"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":62890,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde87"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":10577,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde88"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":28149,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde89"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":16876,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde8a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":10236,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde8b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"221","session":"mike","subject":"0NZH6","rt":30889,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde94"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":47503,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde95"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":17732,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde96"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":11867,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":8532,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde98"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":104790,"answer":"IO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde99"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":7352,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":27980,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":94816,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":36699,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":13675,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":12176,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfde9f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":10598,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdea0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":22166,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdea1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":9807,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdea2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"9PGJL","rt":27759,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":81393,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeac"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":22558,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdead"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":20565,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":29180,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeaf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":27721,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":19518,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":32398,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":36056,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":64035,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":8502,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":24234,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":12048,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":12355,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":8955,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeb9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"0ZCT1","rt":14277,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":50238,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":65879,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":20685,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":9762,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":25691,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":7990,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":40655,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdec9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":37363,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdeca"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":59148,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdecb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":13645,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdecc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":13023,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdecd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":22350,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdece"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":21449,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdecf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":9585,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfded0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"7WP84","rt":16594,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":46691,"answer":"CF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":26916,"answer":"XKE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":71816,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":24152,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":85918,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":10322,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":27242,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":21398,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":23538,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdef9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":7435,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdefa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":8710,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdefb"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":9667,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdefc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":9610,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdefd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":6853,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdefe"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"VT3ZX","rt":130341,"answer":"CX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf07"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":42326,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf08"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":41264,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf09"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":28181,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":48861,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":107787,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":7973,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":18271,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":27761,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf0f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":20898,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf10"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":39207,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf11"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":13923,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf12"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":14141,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf13"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":33485,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf14"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":29333,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf15"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"X0PRP","rt":31415,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf35"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":103059,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf36"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":41664,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf37"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":24798,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf38"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":26327,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf39"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":149093,"answer":"CAZFUGB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":8381,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":19217,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":50447,"answer":"IJE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":43536,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":10390,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf3f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":9571,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf40"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":5883,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf41"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":24168,"answer":"HN"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf42"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":5689,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf43"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"F49JC","rt":40747,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf4c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":41872,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf4d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":42685,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf4e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":28728,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf4f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":33649,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf50"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":60289,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf51"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":102914,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf52"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":57301,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf53"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":41836,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf54"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":18399,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf55"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":8592,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf56"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":18004,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf57"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":18457,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf58"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":19170,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf59"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":13903,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf5a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":2,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"211","session":"mike","subject":"5LHA4","rt":22549,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf63"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":115561,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf64"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":50987,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf65"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":18399,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf66"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":27419,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf67"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":64181,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf68"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":16083,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf69"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":80278,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":92765,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":102088,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":26855,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":15416,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":10227,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf6f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":13831,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf70"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":19492,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf71"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"mike","subject":"WJ5M4","rt":18300,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":28970,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":152708,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":80433,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":203832,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":131965,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf7f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":12296,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf80"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":40097,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf81"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":53522,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf82"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":28785,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf83"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":29340,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf84"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":10166,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf85"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":8813,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf86"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":26792,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf87"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":25328,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf88"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"121","session":"mike","subject":"5WPCV","rt":86843,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf91"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":69242,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf92"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":35585,"answer":"KD"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf93"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":97155,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf94"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":183944,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf95"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":145979,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf96"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":134550,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf97"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":47132,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf98"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":54349,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf99"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":41072,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":37867,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":15726,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":9469,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":23400,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":9719,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdf9f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"3B1TL","rt":29539,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfa8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":37902,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfa9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":189626,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfaa"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":46559,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfab"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":21100,"answer":"AH"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfac"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":29908,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":11054,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":68712,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfaf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":223726,"answer":"FGCO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":210294,"answer":"IM"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":193270,"answer":"IEGCO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":96952,"answer":"MXOLHZND"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":23242,"answer":"IEGCO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":20307,"answer":"ON"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":11510,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfb6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"111","session":"mike","subject":"2JRT6","rt":13077,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfbf"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":19583,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":18253,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":22763,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":33126,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":82945,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":11186,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":25708,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":25750,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":37772,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":34874,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfc9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":12992,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfca"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":8607,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfcb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":37990,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfcc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":22384,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfcd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"JRB0B","rt":35636,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfd6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":25714,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfd7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":30328,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfd8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":15640,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfd9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":30984,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfda"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":16201,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfdb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":25272,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfdc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":22875,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfdd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":47947,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfde"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":26405,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfdf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":10956,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfe0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":7931,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfe1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":19638,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfe2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":11223,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfe3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":8107,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfe4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"HA04H","rt":11955,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfed"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":24024,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":39346,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdfef"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":11827,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":7325,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff1"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":53974,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":51312,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":20858,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":64102,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":20420,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":14534,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":11494,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":4244,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdff9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":22805,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdffa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":31233,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfdffb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"LL91X","rt":34442,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe004"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":64520,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe005"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":36804,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe006"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":12398,"answer":"OJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe007"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":8831,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe008"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":20427,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe009"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":14269,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":33984,"answer":"IJFBMXOZND"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":54150,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":17894,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":26648,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":9575,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe00f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":10919,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe010"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":14111,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe011"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":8006,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe012"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"U6RT2","rt":13484,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe01b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":50322,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe01c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":66794,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe01d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":27799,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe01e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":64332,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe01f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":35176,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe020"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":5818,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe021"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":23667,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe022"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":115650,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe023"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":21995,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe024"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":7693,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe025"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":13533,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe026"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":17983,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe027"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":14776,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe028"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":8034,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe029"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"SC00U","rt":13435,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe032"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":58985,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe033"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":34089,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe034"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":25190,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe035"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":22290,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe036"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":43935,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe037"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":24617,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe038"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":47462,"answer":"FZ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe039"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":52448,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":25856,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":17460,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":20393,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":20157,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":46913,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe03f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":15814,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe040"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"9N508","rt":24740,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe049"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":49703,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":19948,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":15409,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":25795,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":52817,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":13589,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe04f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":44067,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe050"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":54100,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe051"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":68748,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe052"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":10817,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe053"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":13841,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe054"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":12366,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe055"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":46662,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe056"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":14490,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe057"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"T432U","rt":20885,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe060"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":28650,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe061"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":36630,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe062"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":47510,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe063"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":124609,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe064"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":62015,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe065"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":54388,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe066"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":30564,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe067"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":19287,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe068"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":76227,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe069"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":15058,"answer":"J"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe06a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":12225,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe06b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":9136,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe06c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":53996,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe06d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":39628,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe06e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"7DXXS","rt":36734,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe08e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":31022,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe08f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":18236,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe090"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":16065,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe091"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":36787,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe092"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":56006,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe093"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":8658,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe094"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":20085,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe095"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":23871,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe096"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":13087,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe097"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":31639,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe098"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":9589,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe099"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":8838,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe09a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":21761,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe09b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":25183,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe09c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"HUPSU","rt":79506,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0a5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":60471,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":26488,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0a7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":22428,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0a8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":37856,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":225149,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0aa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":9134,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ab"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":12693,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":26824,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":11274,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":16069,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":11187,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0b0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":24164,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0b1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":39371,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0b2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":15379,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0b3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"62ULH","rt":30540,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0bc"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":62843,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0bd"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":25409,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0be"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":24541,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0bf"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":22224,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":31151,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":26781,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c2"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":40854,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c3"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":79853,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c4"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":75790,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":11556,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":16769,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":15843,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c8"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":18897,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0c9"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":11142,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ca"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":1,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"311","session":"alfa","subject":"WXWJ0","rt":34145,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":19758,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":24605,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d5"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":42001,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":89930,"answer":"FU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d7"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":115168,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":7687,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0d9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":20319,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0da"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":46319,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0db"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":19592,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0dc"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":35839,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0dd"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":11537,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0de"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":7339,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0df"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":40746,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0e0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":40248,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0e1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"L5SUE","rt":36944,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ea"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":15654,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0eb"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":30157,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ec"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":45010,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ed"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":99647,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ee"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":119776,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0ef"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":8126,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f0"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":19206,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f1"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":28537,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":20247,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":21453,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":14157,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":20338,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f6"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":25528,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":32415,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe0f8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alpha","subject":"GJ8WG","rt":39558,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe101"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":48775,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe102"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":60757,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe103"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":38283,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe104"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":48546,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe105"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":216185,"answer":"GB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe106"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":9266,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe107"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":22623,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe108"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":35214,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe109"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":20916,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":28834,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":8366,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":11793,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":29698,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":73574,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe10f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"ZZHFE","rt":101177,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe12f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":44532,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe130"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":21596,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe131"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":124868,"answer":"OJ"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe132"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":38737,"answer":"DE"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe133"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":65226,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe134"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":15689,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe135"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":30389,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe136"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":72904,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe137"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":32702,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe138"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":26935,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe139"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":10975,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe13a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":18550,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe13b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":41344,"answer":"ND"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe13c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":27121,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe13d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"diagonal","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"113","session":"alfa","subject":"APXF8","rt":38040,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe146"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":23810,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe147"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":44880,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe148"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":14160,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe149"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":47577,"answer":"FU"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14a"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":128922,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":11194,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":16489,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":43967,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":61555,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe14f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":44234,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe150"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":8058,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe151"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":35186,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe152"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":20468,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe153"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":37873,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe154"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"M444E","rt":315039,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe15d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":24807,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe15e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":26715,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe15f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":34985,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe160"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":50669,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe161"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":299584,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe162"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":21498,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe163"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":18784,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe164"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":75212,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe165"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":28801,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe166"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":38214,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe167"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":12069,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe168"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":9258,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe169"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":30446,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe16a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":17516,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe16b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"77PFQ","rt":165151,"answer":"FG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe174"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":35802,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe175"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":42906,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe176"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":27557,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe177"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":64153,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe178"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":176153,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe179"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":18287,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17a"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":41706,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17b"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":30123,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17c"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":30890,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17d"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":36335,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17e"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":16296,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe17f"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":10675,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe180"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":17613,"answer":"FX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe181"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":27039,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe182"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"Y4FZ1","rt":66889,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe18b"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":131720,"answer":"O"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe18c"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":80885,"answer":"K"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe18d"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":44309,"answer":"F"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe18e"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":16791,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe18f"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":42507,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe190"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":32981,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe191"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":101254,"answer":"XO"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe192"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":141769,"answer":"AGK"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe193"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":44277,"answer":""},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe194"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":24989,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe195"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":28623,"answer":"ML"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe196"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":10260,"answer":"G"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe197"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":26239,"answer":"EF"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe198"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":18647,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe199"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":1,"axis":"full","impasse":2,"explicit":3,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"321","session":"alfa","subject":"K6ZDW","rt":14590,"answer":"KX"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a2"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":1,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":42746,"answer":"A"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a3"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":2,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":32681,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a4"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":3,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":13236,"answer":"Z"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a5"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":4,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":45404,"answer":"U"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a6"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":5,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":185101,"answer":"H"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a7"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":6,"question":"duration","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":9075,"answer":"EG"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a8"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":7,"question":"duration+starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":47974,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1a9"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":8,"question":"duration+contained","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":34789,"answer":"E"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1aa"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":1,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":9,"question":"starttime+before+endtime+during","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":29549,"answer":"I"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1ab"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":10,"question":"ends","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":42937,"answer":"X"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1ac"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":11,"question":"starttime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":12978,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1ad"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":12,"question":"starts","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":10709,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1ae"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":13,"question":"meets","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":22515,"answer":"FB"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1af"},"orth_correct":1,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":14,"question":"endtime","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":18592,"answer":"B"},{"_id":{"$oid":"61816fb1732570cf33cfe1b0"},"orth_correct":0,"correct":0,"axis":"partial","impasse":1,"explicit":1,"q":15,"question":"midpoint","condition":"112","session":"alfa","subject":"J6H2B","rt":117829,"answer":"FO"}]
